theparkingspot.com 2017-03-13

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the Websites and Apps (defined below) provided by TPS Parking Management, LLC d/b/a The Parking Spot, its parent, subsidiaries, related companies and/or controlled affiliates (“The Parking Spot,” “we” or “us”). By “Website(s),” we mean the website maintained at [www.theparkingspot.com](http://www.theparkingspot.com/), the corresponding mobile website, and any other websites or webpages operated by us that link to this Privacy Policy, and by “App(s),” we mean our theParkingSpot™ mobile app, our TPS Shuttle mobile app, and any of our other mobile apps that link to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also applies to information collected from or about you through email and other electronic submissions and communications between you and the Websites and Apps. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that may be collected by third-party sites, content or applications that may link to, or be accessible from or on, the Websites or Apps. Unless specified herein, this Privacy Policy also does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, such as at our facilities or on websites or through mobile applications that do not link to this Privacy Policy. This Policy also does not apply to information collected by third parties, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that we collect from or about users of the Websites and Apps (“you”), how and for what purposes that information may be used and disclosed, the steps we take to protect that information, and the choices that you have regarding whether and how certain information is collected, disclosed and used.

The Websites are operated from and hosted on servers located in the United States in accordance with laws of the United States and the Apps are provided for use in the United States. Users of the Websites and Apps should be aware that the laws of the United States may differ from those of your country of residence. By using the Websites and Apps, participating in any Website or App activities, and/or providing us with your personal information, you: (i) consent to the transfers and processing of any information you provide; (ii) acknowledge that U.S. law provides a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of various jurisdictions including, but not limited to, the European Union; and (iii) understand that we will treat your information in accordance with our Privacy Policy and U.S. law. Consequently, you hereby waive any claims that may arise under the laws and regulations that apply to you in any other jurisdiction.

Please read the following carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. BY USING THE WEBSITES AND BY DOWNLOADING AND/OR USING THE APPS, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND ALSO SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS (available at http://www.theparkingspot.com/terms-and-conditions ) . IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS, DOWNLOAD AND/OR USE THE WEBSITES AND APPS. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently, as it may change from time to time. Click here to read about how changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated to you and made effective.

Click on one of the links below to jump to a specific section:

 1\. Types of Information Collected

2\. How Information is Collected

3. How We Use Your Information

4. How We Share Information

5\.  Cookies and Other Technologies

6\.  Online Tracking / “Do Not Track” Signals

9\.  Children Under 13

10\.  External Links and Third-Party Ads 

911\.  Widgets and Social Media Features

12\.  Location Data

13\.  Protection of Personal Information 

14\.  Notice to California Customers - Your California Privacy Rights 

14\. Your Choices 

15. Changes to this Privacy Policy 

16\.  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

17\.  Contact Us 

**1\. Types of Information Collected**

The Websites and Apps collect both personal information and non-personal or aggregate information from and about you. 

“Personal information” is information by which you can be personally identified or contacted, and may include your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number(s), username, and credit/debit card number and related payment information. Personal information also may include information that may not be personally identifiable standing alone (for example, your reservation dates), but which may become personally identifiable when combined with personal information (for example, your reservation dates combined with your name). Many pages and features on our Websites and Apps can be visited and used without providing any personal information. For other pages, functionalities and services, you may be prompted or invited to provide certain personal information. 

“Non-personal” or “aggregate” information is data that is about you but which does not identify you as an individual and is not linked to your personal information. This may include information such as your reservation dates, communication and other preferences, goods and services purchased and special requests made, information about your computer, devices and Internet connection when you use the Websites and Apps (such as your device type, browser type, IP address, and mobile identifiers such as Apple IDFA and Android Advertising ID), and certain information about your activities while using our Websites and Apps (such as your referring website, click stream data, the search terms you enter, your movement within and interaction with the Websites and Apps, the pages and features you access or visit on the Websites and Apps, the links and ads that you click, and the length of time you spend using the Websites and Apps). Non-personal information also may include personal information that has been de-identified, or in other words, rendered anonymous. For example, survey information that you volunteer may be anonymized and/or aggregated such that it no longer personally identifies you, and would then be considered non-personal or aggregate information. Non-personal information often is collected through the use of cookies, anonymous identifiers, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts, and other similar technologies. Click  here  to learn more about how these types of technologies are used on the Websites and Apps.

**2\. How Information is Collected**

Information is collected from and about you on the Website and Apps through various means, including directly from you when you provide it (for example, via forms that you fill out on the Websites and Apps, through emails and other communications and information that you submit via the Websites and Apps, and through your other activities on the Websites and Apps), and automatically as you navigate through and interact with the Websites, Apps and their content (including via cookies, anonymous identifiers, pixel tags, beacons, scripts, and other tracking technologies).

**Information You Choose to Provide**

We collect information that you choose to provide when you use the Websites and Apps to learn about and use our services, including when you make parking and car care reservations with us, join our loyalty programs, manage your account, request quotes, support or answers to specific questions, subscribe to receive promotional emails, coupons and other information, fill out forms on the Websites and Apps, respond to surveys, and register for and participate in contests and other promotional opportunities. Some of the types of information that we may collect from you include: 

  * Your first name, last name and middle initial;
  * Your email address;
  * Your home and/or business address;
  * Your telephone number(s);
  * Your username and password for membership in our loyalty programs;
  * Your payment information; 
  * Your parking and car care reservation and purchase history with us;
  * Your preferred The Parking Spot facility;
  * Details regarding the activities and transactions you carry out through our Websites and Apps, your preferences and the fulfillment of your requests; 
  * Details and copies of our communications and correspondence with you (including email addresses that you use to correspond with us); 
  * Location information, including your geolocation (click here to learn more about how we use and share location information that you choose to provide on our mobile Website and through our Apps);
  * Your search queries on the Websites and in the Apps; and
  * Any other information you choose to provide.

**Automatically-Collected Information**

When you visit, navigate through and interact with the Websites, Apps and their content (including ads), we, our service providers and other third parties may use technologies (such as cookies, anonymous identifiers, pixels, web beacons, scripts, and other technologies) to automatically collect information about you, your equipment, and your activities on the Websites and Apps. This information includes, but is not limited to: (i) information about your computer, devices and Internet connection when you use the Websites and Apps (such as your device type, browser type, IP address, a mobile identifier associated with a mobile device (such as Apple IDFA and Android Ad ID), and the area of the country where you are located (but not your precise geographic location)); (ii) certain information about your activities while using our Websites and Apps (such as your referring website, click stream data, the search terms you use, your movement within and interaction with the Websites and Apps, the pages and features you access, use or visit on the Websites, the links and ads that you click, and the length of time you spend using the Websites and Apps); and (iii) other information collected by cookies, pixels, web beacons, scripts, and other tracking technologies. To learn more about cookies, pixels, web beacons and other similar technologies, click here to go to the “Cookies and Other Technologies” section below. 

**3\. How We Use Your Information**

We may freely use non-personal information or aggregate information for any lawful purpose. We also may use your personal information for various purposes. In general, we use information, including personal information, from and about you:

  * To develop, deliver, provide and improve our Websites, Apps, services and content;
  * To accommodate your preferences and to customize your experience with our Websites and Apps;
  * To support and process the transactions, and provide the services and support, that you have requested;
  * To register and administer your membership in our loyalty programs;
  * To verify communications from you, respond to your inquiries and otherwise communicate with you;
  * For marketing and promotional purposes, including without limitation sending you promotional materials and offers that we believe may be of interest to you, and managing content and advertising;
  * To enforce our Terms and Conditions and contracts with third parties;
  * To send you important notices, such as communications about reservations and changes to our terms, conditions and policies (because this information is important to your interaction with The Parking Spot, you may not opt-out of receiving these communications); 
  * To prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities or to otherwise comply with applicable laws and regulations;
  * To protect the security or integrity of our Websites, Apps, services and our business and to investigate actual and alleged claims against us; 
  * To conduct auditing, analytics, data analysis, monitor and analyze Website and App traffic and usage, to compile analytics and aggregate statistics about our Websites, Apps, content and advertising campaigns, and to research and evaluate user needs; 
  * To support our business and services, including without limitation through lobbying efforts relating to our business; and
  * For any other purpose that is permissible or required under the law, that is disclosed to you at the point of collection of personal information, or for which you provide your prior consent. 

Payment information (i.e., credit or debit card number, cardholder name, expiration date, EPP code and billing address) is generally obtained only to process a specific transaction. However, members of our loyalty program may choose to link their membership card with a credit card to pre-fill online reservation forms and for convenience of payment. In either case, we only retain debit and credit card information in tokenized form. The Parking Spot may use IP addresses to provide aggregated data to advertisers about the volume of use on the Websites and Apps, to determine your general (but not precise) geographic location, to create and segment audiences and otherwise to target advertising, and to help identify and log potential malicious use of our Websites and Apps. 

We reserve the right to combine personal information we collect on the Websites with data collected or received from other sources. If we combine any non-personal information with personal information that is covered by this Privacy Policy, the combined information will be treated as personal information pursuant to this Privacy Policy as long as it remains combined. We may store personal information for as long as needed for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Policy (which may be indefinitely) or for such period as may be permitted or required by law. We may anonymize information that we have collected or otherwise obtained and use that information in connection with interest-based advertising, to create audience segments and/or for other online advertising purposes. Non-personal information (including anonymized information and other non-personal information that is automatically collected as you navigate through and use the Websites and Apps) is not subject to this Privacy Policy, and we can use and share such information without restriction for any lawful purpose, including without limitation for business and marketing purposes. 

**4\. How We Share Information**

The Parking Spot may freely share and disclose aggregated and other non-personal information (including anonymized information and other non-personal information that is automatically collected as you navigate through and use the Websites) without restriction as permitted by law. The Parking Spot also may share your personal information with and disclose it to third parties for any lawful purpose, including without limitation to: 

  * Your company or organization if you use the Websites and Apps, register for loyalty programs, or use the Websites or Apps to make parking or car care reservations with us, under a corporate or commercial account;
  * Our parent, subsidiaries, related companies and controlled affiliates, who may use such information for our or their own business and marketing purposes, as well as for any of the purposes disclosed in or consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy;
  * Our service providers and vendors who perform services or functions on our behalf, including without limitation hosting, data storage, data processing, security, payment processing, fraud prevention, debt collection, customer service, administering sweepstakes, surveys, advertising and marketing services, public relations, and email and mailing services; 
  * Non-affiliated third parties, including without limitation our co-promotional partners, marketing partners, program partners and other strategic partners, for our or their own marketing and promotional purposes and to administer loyalty programs;
  * A buyer, successor, or other relevant third party in the event of a corporate transaction, merger, acquisition, consolidation, divestiture, spin-off, change in control, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about the users of our Websites or Apps will be among the assets to be transferred;
  * Other third parties in order to fulfill the purpose for which you provide it (including without limitation your credit card issuer); 
  * For any other purpose disclosed when you provide the information; and 
  * Others with your consent. 

We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify you and we may use and disclose any information about or relating to you, including any personal information about you, to third parties without your consent if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order, search warrant, subpoena, or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) otherwise fulfill a government or law enforcement request for information; (4) establish, defend or exercise our legal rights; (5) protect or defend the Websites, Apps, users, or our subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their respective officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, licensors, and partners, in connection with any actual or alleged legal action, claim or dispute; (6) respond to claims that any posting or other content of our Websites or Apps violates the rights of third parties, including without limitation providing information necessary to satisfy the notice and counter-notice procedures pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act; (7) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our Websites’ and Apps’ users or the general public; or (8) enforce compliance with our Terms and Conditions or other contractual obligations. 

**5. Cookies and Other Technologies **

The Parking Spot, its service providers, marketing partners, and other third parties may use cookies, either alone or in conjunction with anonymous identifiers, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts and other technologies, to obtain certain information about Website and App users. A "cookie" is a small text file that can be placed on your computer or other device when you visit a website or use an app. Cookies help to improve your user experience and allow us to analyze our Websites and Apps and to analyze and manage our advertising. While some cookies are deleted when you close your browser (session cookies), others remain even after you close your browsing session (persistent cookies). Cookies alone cannot be used to disclose your individual identity to us. Following are some of the types of cookies that may be used on the Websites and Apps: 

  * Cookies that are necessary for the Websites and Apps to work and/or that enable you to navigate through and take advantage of our Websites, Apps, and their features;
  * Cookies to request HTTP header information in order to make our Websites function correctly, to personalize content presented to you, to better understand how our users use the Websites and Apps and how we can better serve your needs;
  * Cookies to enable features and functionality such as the online reservations process (for example, to remember dates used in reservation searches and to fulfill the reservation), remembering your preferences, allowing members of loyalty programs to sign in without typing their passwords, and personalizing your pages;
  * Cookies to track customer response to our advertisements and content; 
  * Cookies that determine whether your browser is able to receive HTML email messages so that we can determine the appropriate format for you to receive and read email communications from us; 
  * Analytics cookies to provide data about how users interact with Website and App content and advertising campaigns, such as how many people use our Websites and Apps, which pages and features they visit and use, how long they stay there, how visitors come to our Websites ( _e.g._ through a link from another website or via a search engine), and also to collect information about how users use our Websites and Apps. Analytics cookies may be used alone or in conjunction with unique identifiers, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts, and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Websites and Apps or interact with our ads on other websites and apps. 

o We use Google Analytics to measure and report how users interact with our Websites and/or Apps for the purposes of understanding and optimizing web usage, for business and market research, measuring conversion tracking, and managing, measuring, and optimizing the effectiveness of our content and advertising campaigns. For more information about Google Analytics and how it collects and processes data, please see “[How Google Uses Data When You Use Our Partners’ Sites or Apps](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).” For more information about how Google Analytics uses cookies to measure user interactions on websites, click [here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected about your visits to the Websites is restricted by Google’s [Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/policies/terms/) and the [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Websites by disabling cookies on your browser. If you do not want your website visit data reported by the Google Analytics JavaScript, you also can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. This add-on instructs the Google Analytics JavaScript to prohibit sending website visit information to Google Analytics, but does not prevent information from being sent to the website itself or in other ways to other website analytics services. Click [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en) if you would like to learn more about the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, and click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) to install the opt-out browser add-on to opt-out of Google Analytics on the web.

  * Advertising Cookies to manage, target and serve ads through third-party advertising technology when you visit our Websites and use our Apps and when you visit other websites and use other apps. 

o Third parties, including advertising networks and other vendors, also may use anonymous identifiers, cookies, pixel tags, beacons, scripts, and other technologies, to track and collect information, including non-personal demographic information, about you and your interests and activities when you visit our Websites and other websites or view or interact with one of the advertisements they place on various websites or mobile platforms. The information gathered by these third parties is used to make predictions about your characteristics, interests or preferences and to display advertisements and content on our Websites and across the Internet tailored to your apparent interests. This is known as interest-based advertising. We allow third-party companies and others to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Websites and use our Apps. These companies may collect and use non-personal information (such as, for example, hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. Demographic or other interest data may also be associated with your browsers or devices when you use the Websites and Apps, and such data may also be used online to serve you advertisements targeted based on your presumed interests. 

o We use Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google AdWords to show you our ads as you browse other websites around the Internet. The Remarketing service delivers our ads through the Google Display Network, which includes both Google.com pages and the sites of trusted publishers. Click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types/) for more information on the types of advertising cookies that Google uses, and [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/) for more information about how Google uses advertising cookies. Click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) to read the Google privacy policy. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies and/or customize Google display network ads by visiting the Ads Settings at <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. Alternatively, you can opt-out of Remarketing by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. We also use the DoubleClick cookies and/or pixels in connection with Google’s Remarketing service. To learn more about DoubleClick cookie, click [here](https://support.google.com/ds/answer/2839090?hl=en&ref_topic=2473095). If you want to permanently opt out of the DoubleClick cookie, you can install the DoubleClick opt out extension by clicking [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjj6y8lzk-Kvx-t2tPWloCukcymal01nyHd4cBmyWciWf2CBiODknfNsIP_jEew-oaJ6HzQiUFwlWcUMiHlErh1VfK60fpLGtQs72fjhGVdye5XdcM4lJe7d_YGyXnQbXUxk2EQoVt2djdNdzKGiCATQqAtNp0e4jIMJ4s1uTrrLOEuozB4K6Db0m3B3zk37svYTQZ). To serve ads in our mobile applications, Google may use anonymous identifiers. These perform similar functions to cookies. To learn more about how to opt out of interest-based advertising for your mobile device, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

o We also use information collected through cookies, anonymous identifiers, pixels, web beacons, scripts and other technologies to collect, analyze and segment data from websites and other sources to help us provide more effective advertising. For example, we may use data that is available from public or commercial sources and combine it with other data we have collected or received about a user or the user’s device. We work with third-party advertising service partners and platforms that help us provide more effective advertising by, for example, helping us to deliver ads to people who are most likely to be interested in seeing them, keep track of the number of users who saw a particular ad or visited a particular page on our Websites or Apps, and analyze the effectiveness of our ads. While the companies we work with may change from time to time, click on the following links to learn more about the practices of some of the companies we may work with and the choices they may offer with respect to advertising: [Lotame](http://www.lotame.com/), [LiveRamp](http://liveramp.com/), [Adacado](http://www.adacado.com/) and [The Trade Desk](http://www.thetradedesk.com/). 

o Some digital advertising companies also are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance, each of which offer a single location to opt-out of certain ad targeting from member companies. To learn more about interest-based advertising generally as well as your options for opting out, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. Please keep in mind that even if you opt out of receiving ads tailored to your apparent interests, you will continue to see ads from online advertising networks. However, those networks will not be able to apply any of your apparent ad preferences and the ads that you see therefore may be less relevant to your interests.

    * Social media cookies may be placed by social media platforms (such as Facebook, Twitter, etc.) for authentication purposes and/or to collect certain information about your visits to and use of our Websites and Apps through social media widgets. Such third-party social media sites are responsible for those cookies and how they process the data they collect and their practices are governed by their own privacy policies. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the applicable third-party social media site before using their widgets or functionalities. 

Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. For more information on how to manage browser cookies, see [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You also can check your mobile device’s built-in settings to find out how to turn off cookies on your mobile device. Some mobile devices also might store cookies in areas that are app-specific, which cannot be controlled by browser settings. Check your app settings options on your mobile device to find out how to manage or delete cookies that may be stores in these other areas. Please keep in mind, however, that you may not be able to access the full functionality of our Websites and Apps if cookies are disabled. Please also note that disabling or clearing cookies also may affect cookie-based opt-outs by either preventing you from using such cookie-based opt-outs or clearing opt-outs that you previously set, in which case you would have to revisit the applicable pages and renew your opt-out after clearing cookies. 

The Parking Spot, its service providers and other third parties also may use web beacons and pixel tags, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are placed in the code of a web page. These technologies may be used, for example, to allow The Parking Spot and its service providers to send emails to you in a format you can read and to count users who have visited our Websites or used our Apps, seen our ads, opened our emails or clicked on any links in our emails. These technologies also may be used by The Parking Spot and its service providers to better target and personalize ads and to track ad campaigns. For example, pixel tags, web beacons and other technologies may allow third-party ad networks to recognize a unique cookie on your web browser or mobile device. This enables us to learn which ads bring users to our Websites and Apps. The information collected may tell the third-party ad network what other websites you have visited that are associated with the network. This information may be used for the purpose of managing, targeting and personalizing ads on our Websites and Apps and other websites and apps based on those interests. 

We, our service providers and other third parties may analyze the information derived from cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts and other technologies and match or combine that information with data provided by you or collected or received from public and commercial sources. Please note that to the extent that third parties are using pixel tags, cookies, beacons, scripts or other tracking technologies on our Websites and Apps, The Parking Spot does not control the use of those technologies or the resulting information, the use of which are governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. 

**6. Online Tracking / “Do Not Track” Signals**

Some web browsers may give you the ability to enable a “Do Not Track” setting that sends a special signal to the websites you encounter while web browsing that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, and The Parking Spot does not respond to web browser “Do Not Track” signals at this time. If we do so in the future, we will update this Privacy Policy to describe how we respond to such signals. We may work with third parties that use tracking technologies on the Websites and Apps, including in order to serve tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These and other third parties may collect information about your activity on the Websites and Apps and other websites and apps over time, as well as your interaction with our advertising and other communications, and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications based on your apparent interests, which is known as interest-based advertising. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/> or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). To learn more about Do Not Track, visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>. Click here to go to the “Cookies and Other Technologies” to read more about interest-based advertising and other online advertising.

**7. Children Under 13**

The Parking Spot encourages parents and guardians to spend time with minors online, so as to be fully familiar with the websites they visit and the apps they use. Our Websites and Apps are not directed to individuals under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, do not use the Websites or Apps and do not provide us with any personal information of any kind whatsoever. The Parking Spot does not knowingly obtain and does not wish to collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13. We also do not knowingly solicit or contact children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to use our Websites or Apps. It is possible, through fraud or deception, that we may receive personal information from an individual under the age of 13. If we are notified or otherwise become aware of this, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information in accordance with applicable law. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and you believe your child has provided personal information on our Websites or through our Apps without your consent that you would like us to delete, please contact us at [privacy@theparkingspot.com](mailto:feedback@theparkingspot.com) or by writing to us at: The Parking Spot, 200 W. Monroe St., Suite 1500, Chicago, IL, 60606,Attention: Legal Department. 

**8. External Links and Third-Party Ads**

The Websites and Apps may contain links to or ads for third-party websites, apps and content that we do not control or maintain. By clicking on those links or ads, you are visiting sites and content that are outside of our control. Be aware that those websites collect information and operate according to their own privacy practices and policies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites or ads and we are not responsible for the content found on or the actions or privacy practices employed by any other website or app. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites and apps to understand how they collect, use and disclose personal information before submitting any such information to those websites or apps. If you have any questions about the privacy practices of other websites or apps, you should contact the relevant parties controlling these websites apps for more information.

**9. Widgets and Social Media Features**

The Websites and Apps may include social media features such as the Facebook “Like” button, widgets such as a “Share This” button, or interactive mini-programs that run on our Websites or Apps to provide specific services from another company. These third-party features may collect information about you, like your IP address and the page(s) you visit on the Websites or Apps, as well as personal information, such as your email address. They also may place cookies or other tracking mechanisms on your computer or device to, for example, enable the widget to function properly. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policies of the third-party social media platforms that provide them. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the applicable third-party social media sites before using their widgets and other functionalities. 

**10. Location Data **

Our mobile Website and theParkingSpot™ App allow you to use the “Find a Location” feature to find one of our facilities. To use this feature you must enable location services on your mobile device. If you choose to use this feature you will be asked if you want to use location services. If you agree, the Google Maps API will be used to display a zoomed in area on a map “pinning” your geolocation as well as the location of The Parking Spot’s facilities. You also can select one of our facilities from a drop down menu and, if you have enabled location services on your device and agree that you want to use those services, you also can use Google Maps to provide you turn-by-turn driving directions to The Parking Spot facility you have selected. Both the map and driving directions features are provided by Google Maps and it is your choice whether to use these features. We do not control Google Maps, and your use of that functionality is subject to Google’s Privacy Policy, as amended by Google from time to time, which can be reviewed [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en_us/policies/privacy/). Most mobile devices provide users the ability to disable location services, and you will need to enable location services for Google Maps if you wish to use that functionality on the mobile website or mobile application. Most likely, these controls are located in your device's settings menu. 

Our TPS Shuttle App allows you to track the location of our parking shuttles at the airports we serve. To use this feature you must enable location services on your mobile device. If you choose to use this feature you will be asked if you want to use location services. If you agree, your geolocation (i.e., your latitudinal and longitudinal coordinates) will be sent from your device, allowing us to determine at which airport you are located. You are then prompted to select which of our facilities serving that airport you are using. We will use your geolocation information to show you a map of the real-time location of our parking shuttles serving the facility you are using and to locate you on our dispatch map so that we can see where and for how long you have been waiting for one of our shuttles. We do not associate your geolocation data with any personal information or share it with third parties other than to fulfill the purpose for which you provide your geolocation information. 

**11. Protection of Personal Information**

We take reasonable steps to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse, alteration and destruction of the personal information under our control. For example, our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures. We also encrypt data when you make a reservation through the Websites and certain Apps. Since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, the storage and communication of personal information can never be completely secure, including without limitation with respect to computer viruses, malicious software and hacker attacks. We therefore cannot and do not guarantee or warrant that information that you transmit to us, or any communications conducted on or through the Websites or Apps, is or will be totally secure. We are not responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. For your own privacy protection, we urge you to keep all passwords (including passwords that you may need to access certain portions of the Websites and Apps) confidential. We also recommend that you do not include any confidential or sensitive personal information in any emails that you send to us. If you become aware of any breach of the terms of this Privacy Policy or of the security of the Websites or Apps, please notify us. 

**12. Notice to California Customers - Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, individual customers who reside in California and who have an existing business relationship with us may request information about our disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an email to [privacy@theparkingspot.com](mailto:feedback@theparkingspot.com)with the subject heading “California Privacy Rights.” .” In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California privacy rights requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted to addresses other than the email address specified in this paragraph. 

**13.Your Choices **

You can manage your information in the following ways:

    * **Choosing the Personal Information That You Provide**. You decide whether to volunteer certain personal information when using the Websites and Apps. However, while you can access and use the Websites and Apps without providing certain personal information to us, providing certain personal information is required to use some of the features, functionalities and services offered through the Websites and Apps, including, but not limited to, registering for loyalty programs, making a reservation, or participating in sweepstakes or other prize contests.
    * **Account Information**. If you have registered for our theSpotClub® loyalty program, you can login to your account and may be able to change or update certain information and preferences to keep all such data accurate, complete and up-to-date. You also can contact us as described in the “Contact Us” section below to update certain information and preferences, but please allow up to four (4) weeks to process requests such requests. If you request that we delete required account information from our system (e.g. name, mailing address, email address or telephone number(s)), your account and all points in that account accumulated under theSpotClub loyalty program will be terminated without further notice.
    * **Cookies**. You can set your web browser to refuse browser cookies or to alert you when such cookies are being sent. For more information on how to manage browser cookies, click here or check your browser’s Help menu. You also can check your mobile device’s built-in settings to find out how to turn off cookies on your mobile device. Some mobile devices also might store cookies in areas that are app-specific, which cannot be controlled by browser settings. Check your app settings options on your mobile device to find out how to manage or delete cookies that may be stores in these other areas. Although you may disable or refuse browser cookies and still access the Websites and Apps, disabling or refusing cookies may prevent or inhibit you from taking advantage of certain features or visiting certain areas of the Websites. Please also note that disabling or clearing cookies may affect cookie-based opt-outs by either preventing you from using such opt-outs or clearing cookie-based opt-outs that you previously set, in which case you would have to revisit the applicable pages and renew your opt-out after clearing cookies. Managing cookies also will not disable non-cookie technologies present on the Websites and Apps.
    * **Interest-Based Ads and Other Online Advertising**. Visit [ http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn about your options for opting out of interest-based advertising. To learn more about how to opt-out of interest-based advertising for your mobile device, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You can specifically opt-out of Google's use of cookies and/or customize Google display network ads by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager at https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of Remarketing with Google by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. If you want to permanently opt-out of the DoubleClick cookie, you can install the DoubleClick opt-out extension by clicking [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjj6y8lzk-Kvx-t2tPWloCukcymal01nyHd4cBmyWciWf2CBiODknfNsIP_jEew-oaJ6HzQiUFwlWcUMiHlErh1VfK60fpLGtQs72fjhGVdye5XdcM4lJe7d_YGyXnQbXUxk2EQoVt2djdNdzKGiCATQqAtNp0e4jIMJ4s1uTrrLOEuozB4K6Db0m3B3zk37svYTQZ). Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser or update or re-install your current browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choices. Please also keep in mind that even if you opt-out of receiving ads tailored to your apparent interests, you will continue to see ads from online advertising networks. However, those networks will not be able to apply any of your apparent ad preferences and the ads that you see therefore may be less relevant to your interests.
    * **Promotional Emails**. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving future promotional emails from us by following the “unsubscribe” instructions contained in any promotional emails that you receive from us. You also may contact us as described in the “Contact Us” section below if you want to opt-out from receiving future marketing emails from us. Please note that it may take up to ten (10) days to process your opt-out request. Please also be aware that even if you have opted-out of receiving future promotional emails from us, you may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as transactional or relationship messages, and messages about your account and profile. Please also note that we may not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of those third parties to whom we already provided your personal information as of the date of your opt-out request

**14. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may change or update this Privacy Policy in the future. The effective date is identified at the top of this Privacy Policy. Any revisions to this Privacy Policy will take effect immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy. If we make material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address you provided when you registered for our loyalty program, if applicable), by posting a notice on the Websites and Apps, or by other means. You should regularly review the current version of this Privacy Policy. Use of the Websites and Apps following posted changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy then in effect. If you continue to access or use the Websites and Apps after we have updated the Privacy Policy, your access or use of the Websites and Apps after the date such changes are effective shall be deemed as your agreement to be bound by those changes whether or not you have had actual notice of, or have read, the relevant changes. If you do not agree to be bound by the relevant changes, you should not continue to access or use the Website or Apps. 

**15. Contact Us**

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us by email at [feedback@theparkingspot.com](mailto:privacy@theparkingspot.com) or by writing to us at: The Parking Spot, 200 W. Monroe St., Suite 1500, Chicago, IL, 60606, Attention: Legal Department.
